<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CrypTxt</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>

    <string name="LOGIN_PREFS">uw.edu.tcss450.team6.cryptxt.PREFS</string>
    <string name="LOGGEDIN">loggedin</string>
    <string name="LOGIN_FILE"> uw.edu.tcss450.team6.cryptxt.LOGIN_FILE</string>

    <string-array name="cipher_array">
        <item>Shift</item>
        <item>Vigenere</item>
        <item>Substitution</item>
        <item>Permutation</item>
        <item>Advanced</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="helpString">
    Cryptography: Using mathematics to alter messages to hide their meaning.
    Encryption: Using a Cryptographic function to hide words going
    from plaintext to
    ciphertext.
    Decryption: Using a Cryptographic function to reveal hidden words going
    from
    ciphertext to plaintext.
    Key: The combination of words or letters that are used to encrypt or decrypt
    the message.
    Cloud: A reference to being saved on the server.
    Plaintext: Text that has not been encrypted and can be read by a human.
    Ciphertext: Text that has been encrypted and cannot yet be read by a human.
    Cipher Alphabet: Numbers corresponding to each letter, such as:
    a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z
    0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25
    Shift Cipher: An encryption method that shifts each plaintext letters by a certain
    number of characters, specified by the key from the cipher alphabet
    (a=0, b=1, c=2, … z=25). So, j shifted 3, would go from 9 to 12, resulting
    in the letter m in ciphertext. (Going past 25 wraps around.)
    Vigenère Cipher: An encryption method that uses a word as they key, with each letter
    being the amount to shift each character in the plaintext.
    (banana = 1, 0, 13, 0, 13, 0 would shift the first letter by 1, second letter
    by 0, third by 13, etc., and repeat on the 7th letter (since banana is 6
    letters long)
    Substitution Cipher: An encryption method that swaps each letter of an alphabet with
    another letter, such as below would change a to z, h to s, etc.:
    a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z
    z y x w v u t s r q p o n m l k j i h g f e d c b a
    Permutation Cipher: An encryption method that swaps the placement of letters in a certain
    pattern (for example, put the 1st letter in the 4th position, 2nd letter in
    the 6th position, etc.) If the key is {3,5,1,6,4,2}, then “thread” would
    encrypt to “ratdeh” with
    ‘r’ being the 3rd letter, ‘a’ being the 5th etc.
    Advanced Cipher: A combination encryption method that combines the substitution and
    permutation ciphers for extra security.
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
